[Music]
ICC Lombard Company is continuously
running various campaigns.
In this sequence, on Thursday, helmets were distributed among hundreds of bike riders
at Phod Company Chowk in Purnia, courtesy of ESIC Umred Company.
On this occasion,
Sadar CDPO Pushkar Kumar,
Station Incharge Anil Kumar Singh and
many other police officers along with police
personnel were present. On this occasion,
people riding bikes on the road were made aware about road safety by the people of ICC Lombard Company
and the administration
and
people were advised to wear helmets.
During this, Sadar CDPO Pushkar Kumar
distributed helmets to many people with his own hands and made them
aware about road safety.
While talking to the media, Sudhar
CDPO said that the work being done by ICC Lombard Company is
very commendable.
He said that this is a very good first
that people are being made aware about road safety and
helmets are being distributed.
Today, with awareness about road safety,
he said that it is a festival and in such a situation, brothers
go to their sisters' houses to tie Rakhi. If the brother is unsafe and has an
accident and the sister is near  If you cannot buy Rakhi, then
ICC, which deals in
insurance, deals in general insurance, has distributed free helmets
with its support to give the message
to those people
that helmet is very important for you.
We are not fining these people today
because it is Rakshabandhan, if a brother is going to his
sister's place and if we fine him, it will
not be good, so free distribution is being done by ICC Lomd.
This is small
but even those who have not been fined,
I will definitely request them to wear helmets
and ensure their safety.
You have to wear helmets for your
own safety, not to save yourself from fines, and under this campaign,
today here in Dr. Thana, Inspector Sahib
is Anil Kumar Singh, I am there, other sub-
inspectors and all the
managers of ICC Bank are there
and this good and meaningful work done by INLD,
we also thank you very much for this.